Guide to the Kilpatrick Collection of Cherokee Manuscripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Notebook #6 "Uwedasat Collection"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Letter to "Dear friend", undated (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Medical formula (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Medical formula (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - Medical formula, annotated with the name "Nancy [C?]", undated (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - Medical formula, annotated with the number 57, undated (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 250)
    Variant of the text 1 "To doctor for insects," published in transliterated Cherokee and English translation in Notebook.
  - Recto: Medical formula, annotated with the number 25; Verso: Medical formula, annotated with the number 26, undated (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - Tsegi [Jack]. Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 257)
    On verso of one note: "Gray Bros, Welling Okla."
    One note written on a printed order form
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Medical formula, written in a printed invoice, undated (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 260)
    Includes a list of textiles, "cloth white 2 yds..."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - Medical formula, including a list of supplies in English, undated (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Medical formula (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Medical formula (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Charles Ugasedi. Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Medical formula, 1900 July 14 (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Medical formula, with lines numbered 1 through 11, undated (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 294)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Letter to John, in English, 1901 November 2 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    One note is pinned to a letter in English dated 1901 November 2
  - Medical formula, on paper printed with "Scripture [Memoranda]", undated (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Recto: medical formula; verso: fragment of a letter in English, undated (Box 4, Folder 301)
    Letter on verso refers to "frauds alleged to have been perpetrated upon the Eastern band of Cherokee Indians in North Carolina...," and to "Maj. Erwin, Asst. Dist. Attorney"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Medical formula, 1900 July 14 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - [Dewisi?]. Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 321)
- Notebook #7 "JFK Notes and Scraps"
  - Binder cover "7 JFK Notes and scraps" (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Wili and Ani (Will and Ann). "Kilpatrick folk formula collection," in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 2 pages, undated (Box 4, Folder 323)
    Before starting on a trip
    For a foreign object in the eye
    To cure a sty
    To cure a wart
    For hiccoughs
    For the new moon
    For a game of hide-and-seek
  - Keladi Uwosodi. Folk formulae in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    For a burn
    For a chop wound
    For a bee sting
    For a centipede bite
    For a toothache
    For a cut
    For a burn with hot water
    For a snake bite
    For a headache
  - Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper). Collection I (incantations), autograph manuscript with transliteration and translation in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 5 pages, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    Includes biographical notes about Ed Handle, whose texts Kilpatrick recorded through his daughter Minnie Jumper.
    To gain affection
    For toothache and earache
    Formula for a burn
    For disposing of milk teeth
    For protection in battle
    Natchez spell to lure deer
  - Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper). Collection II (incantations), autograph manuscript with transliteration and translation in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 5 pages, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    For male attractiveness
    For headache
    Cure for a centipede bite
    For good luck
    Natchez song
    Cherokee song
  - Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper). Medicine Collection, 4 pages, 1963 July-August (Box 4, Folder 327)
    Includes "for making rain" and several medical formulae.
  - Recto: List of people who died in 1875 August-October; Verso: Excerpt of a Cherokee text, transliteration and translation in Jack Kilpatrick's hand., undated (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Letsili Unega (Rachel White) Collection, "To Use the Crystal", 1966 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Letsili Unega (Rachel White), cure for a toothache, 1966 July 25 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    "Written in a book in the autograph of Siquanida [Dildegi] (Willie Jumper)."
  - Swimmer, Lizzie. For a poultice to remove a foreign object introduced by sorcery, 1963 August 12 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - [Lives?], Taylor, three medical formulae in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 August 13 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Uwodige Gigagei (George Washington). Letter to Jack Kilpatrick and medical formulae, 1965 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper). "For sticking a nail in the foot", 1964 (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Medical formula, "For Fish," "For a Burn," "For Toothache", 1962 April 22
    "Written down on Easter Sunday 1962, at the home of Lois Ishcomer"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - Tsuyohvsvi (Dollie Duncan), Medical formula, 1940 December 12 (Box 5, Folder 340)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - Recto: Letter fragments, Rosie, Dallas, Texas, to "Dearest Mother and All"; Verso: Medical formula, 4 pages, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - Recto, from "Your Mom," Welling, Oklahoma, to "Dear Russell"; Verso, continuation of letter; Bible verses in Cherokee with references in English; medical formula, 1965 April 8, undated (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - Recto: Letter from Rosie, Dallas, Texas, to "Dear Daddy"; Verso: medical formula, 2 pages, 1965 April 30, undated (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper), Meeting notes, [1966 March 11?] (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - [Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper)?], Medical formula, circa 1966 (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 353)
    Illustrated with the number 5 and a radiant sun with a heart at its center.
  - [Siquanida Dilidegi (Willie Jumper)?], Medical formula, three pages, undated (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - Recto: Letter to "Dearest Mary"; Verso: medical formula, 1965 October 25, undated (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - Recto: Letter to "Dear Lillie"; Verso: Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - Medical formula, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 357)
    Written on the back of a printed program for the Park Hill Presbyterian Church Homecoming, 1965 October 10.
  - Recto: Letter, Dallas Texas, to "Dear Mother"; Verso: Medical formula, 1965 November 10, undated (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: letter to "Everybody", undated (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - Recto: Medical formula, illustrated with a drawing of the sun on the horizon; Verso: letter signed "Your Daughter Always, Rosie", undated (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Letter signed "Rosie", undated (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: letter to "Dearest Mother," dated 1965 February 10, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: letter to "My Dearest Mother," dated 1965 March 17, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - Note, on printed sheet of "Study Assignments", undated (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Letter to "Dear Daddy," dated 1965 October 25, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - Recto: Journal entry or personal note; Verso: Practice writing of numbers 1-9, undated (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Erased list of numbered entries from "Ruth", undated (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - [Diganiyisgi?]. Medical formula, begins with the number 4., undated (Box 5, Folder 368)
    Accompanied by a note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand: "Diganiyisgi ugwe I."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 369)
  - Vann, Jim. Medical formula, 45 numbered lines on 2 pages, illustrated with drawings of an arrowhead and sun on horizon, 1963 June 29 (Box 5, Folder 370)
    "Copied by William Jumper from document in possession of Jim Vann, Je. 29, 1963"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 371)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 372)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - Beamer, George. Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - Medical formula, on stationery illustrated with the image of a flower and the phrase "I strive to console thee", undated (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - Recto: Nvwodi (Ada Bunch). Medical formula; Verso: Letter to "Dear Ada", circa 1963 (Box 5, Folder 385)
    Accompanied by a note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand: "Ada Bunch coll. I (Nvwodi) Je. 25, '63"
  - Medical formula, on Ideal Cement Company stationery, undated (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Watt, _____. Financial notes and grocery list on two pages, undated. (Box 5, Folder 393)
    Accompanied by a note identifying the author as "Wadi" (Watt).
  - Siquanida. Medical formula, on an envelope from the Internal Revenue Service, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Siquanida. Medical formula, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 400)
    Accompanied by note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand: "Sugar Mt. giduwa Ritual Coll. (obtained from Siquanida Aug. '63)."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 403)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 404)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 405)
  - Medical formula (Box 5, Folder 406)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 407)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - Recto: letter in English from Silas Copeland to "Catcher" dated 1948 January 20; verso: medical formula (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - Recto: Medical formula; verso: shopping list, undated (Box 5, Folder 410)
    Annotation on recto: Charlotte Blossom, Locust Grove, Oklahoma
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - Medical formula on recto and verso, citing the date 1946 March 30, undated (Box 5, Folder 412)
    Annotation on recto: Ned Young, Hulbert Okla., R.I. B. 32 A
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - Recto: printed receipt completed in manuscript for a purchase by Henry Watt from R. J. Rhea, dealer in dry goods; verso: medical formula, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 414)
    Annotated on verso: "this for how to conging bad burn in skin"
  - Medical formulae on recto and verso, undated (Box 5, Folder 415)
  - Medical formulae on recto and verso, 1925 November 26 (Box 5, Folder 416)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 417)
    Accompanied by a note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand: "[Henila?] Wadi" (Henry Watt)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 418)
  - Medical formula on recto and verso of printed ledger sheet, 1929 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 419)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 420)
  - Medical formula with water damage, undated (Box 5, Folder 421)
  - Recto: medical formula; verso: list, undated (Box 5, Folder 422)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 423)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 424)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 425)
    Annotated on verso: "7652"
  - Medical formula with vocables, undated (Box 5, Folder 426)
    Accompanied by a note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand: "Unidentified Coll. I"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - Recto: list of names and numbers; verso: numerical calculations, undated (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - Recto: medical formula; verso: doodles including drawing of a bird, 1945 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 431)
    Annotated in English: "conging word"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 432)
  - Bill of sale for medical texts, undated (Box 6, Folder 433)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 434)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 435)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 436)
  - Bible verse notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 437)
  - Medical formula, receipt, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 438)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 439)
  - Medical formula or note, undated (Box 6, Folder 440)
  - Medical formula or note, undated (Box 6, Folder 441)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 442)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 443)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 444)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 445)
  - George Draper address, regarding acres of cotton, undated (Box 6, Folder 446)
  - Financial notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 447)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 448)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 449)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 450)
    Annotated "To kill," in English
  - Financial notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 451)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 452)
  - Financial, undated (Box 6, Folder 453)
    Annotated "Sam Skad" at the top of the page, and "Henry Budd" in the middle
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 454)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 455)
  - Financial notes, items and value, undated (Box 6, Folder 456)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 457)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 458)
  - Financial notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 459)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 460)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 461)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 462)
  - Financial notes, 1949 October 10 (Box 6, Folder 463)
  - Financial notes, 1941 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 464)
    Annoted in English, "19 Head - Cattle Sold"
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 465)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 466)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 467)
  - Personal note, undated (Box 6, Folder 468)
    Annotated on verso in English: "Saturday Evening"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 469)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 470)
  - Medical formula, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 471)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 472)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 473)
  - Financial, undated (Box 6, Folder 474)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 475)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 476)
  - Song: vocables, undated (Box 6, Folder 477)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 478)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 479)
  - Financial notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 480)
    Annotated in English: "Gun shell, gage 12, no. 4 shot, one box"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 481)
  - Grocery list, undated (Box 6, Folder 482)
  - Song: vocables, undated (Box 6, Folder 483)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 484)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 485)
  - Song: vocables, undated (Box 6, Folder 486)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 487)
  - Recto: Note in English; Verso: numeric figures, undated (Box 6, Folder 488)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 489)
  - Note: "81_73", undated (Box 6, Folder 490)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 491)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 492)
  - Medical formula, fragment, undated (Box 6, Folder 493)
  - Unidentified fragment, undated (Box 6, Folder 494)
  - Fragment of a receipt from a funeral home, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 495)
    Writing is largely illegible due to water damage.
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 496)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 497)
  - Grocery list, undated (Box 6, Folder 498)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 499)
  - Song, undated (Box 6, Folder 500)
- Notebook #8: "Medicine Men of the Cherokee"
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 6-10: In process material. Research use may require advance notice. Contact the Manuscript Unit for further information.
  - Green binder cover, "Medicine Men of the Cherokee", undated (Box 6, Folder 501)
  - Notebook containing financial records, undated (Box 6, Folder 502)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 503)
  - Wolf, Scott. Medical formula, "Bad Medicine", 1910 (Box 6, Folder 504)
  - Notebook, including unidentified text in Cherokee, list of names in English, and financial figures, undated (Box 6, Folder 505)
    List of names includes individuals with surnames Bigacorn, Proctor, and Scott.
  - Writing practice, with short explanation of presentation at the bottom, undated (Box 6, Folder 506)
  - Journal entry or note, undated (Box 6, Folder 507)
  - List of food products and prices, 1915 December (Box 6, Folder 508)
  - Watt, Samuel. Personal history., undated (Box 6, Folder 509)
  - Letter, 1922 September 25 (Box 6, Folder 510)
  - Letter or note, 1923 September 18 (Box 6, Folder 511)
  - Letter, 1916 July 22 (Box 6, Folder 512)
  - Letter documenting a financial transaction, 1918 November (Box 6, Folder 513)
  - Business letter, 1925 April 3 (Box 6, Folder 514)
  - Recto: Financial notes; Verso: Cherokee vocabulary for months, 1916 September 7 (Box 6, Folder 515)
  - Campbell, John. Receipt, undated (Box 6, Folder 516)
  - Moore, L. C.? Historical narrative, circa 1912 (Box 6, Folder 517)
  - Historical account, 4 pages, 1921 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 518)
  - Recto: Printed receipt from Tuel & Kincaid, Stilwell, Indian Territory; Verso: Documentation of a financial transaction, undated (Box 6, Folder 519)
  - Letter or note, 1912 August 9 (Box 6, Folder 520)
  - Unidentified Cherokee text with numerical figures, circa 1916 (Box 6, Folder 521)
    Annotated "For Waterdown, Barber, Okla. 9/21/1916"
  - Obituary, 1902 March 21 (Box 6, Folder 522)
  - Wolf, David (Dewi Waya). Note, undated (Box 6, Folder 523)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 524)
  - Obituary for Mary Wadi (Meli Wadi), circa 1926 (Box 6, Folder 525)
  - List of names and numbers, undated (Box 6, Folder 526)
  - List of names and dates, undated (Box 6, Folder 527)
  - Historical, community record, 1913 February 5 (Box 7, Folder 531)
  - Historical, scrap of community record, undated (Box 7, Folder 532)
  - "Old Time Indian Religion Nite Hawk," with eight sets of dates and numbers, undated (Box 7, Folder 533)
  - Unidentified, 1922 January 15 (Box 7, Folder 534)
  - Obituary, circa 1891 (Box 7, Folder 535)
  - Sermon?, 1914 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 536)
  - Death record, undated (Box 7, Folder 537)
  - Birth record, undated (Box 7, Folder 538)
  - Syllabary practice, undated (Box 7, Folder 539)
  - Unidentified, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 540)
  - Smith, Redbird., no year October 11 (Box 7, Folder 541)
  - Lodge, John. Speech?, undated (Box 7, Folder 542)
  - Speech? Letter?, undated (Box 7, Folder 543)
  - Speech? Letter?, undated (Box 7, Folder 544)
  - Speech? Letter?, undated (Box 7, Folder 545)
  - Speech? Letter?, undated (Box 7, Folder 546)
  - Envelope, annotated "Anigituwesi Documents", circa 1962 (Box 7, Folder 547)
  - Rattler, Rider. Medicine book, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 548)
  - Wolf, Arch. Medicine book, circa 1926 (Box 7, Folder 549)
  - Duncan Book 6, circa 1935 (Box 7, Folder 550)
  - Duncan Book 7, circa 1920 (Box 7, Folder 551)
  - Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Uwedasadi xxxvii", undated (Box 7, Folder 552)
  - "Building law this paper", undated (Box 7, Folder 553)
  - Unidentified list, 1930 September 11 (Box 7, Folder 554)